PARTH MALI



1210- 2 Forest Laneway, North York, ON, M2N 5X7 (+1(437)-777-7064





parthmali1597@gmail.com parth.mali@wonderbrands.com

OBJECTIVE

Computer Professional with a focus on results who is enthusiastic about developing new expertise, making connections, and acquiring knowledge. My career goal is to lend a position that will allow me to directly contribute to the organization's growth while taking my career to new heights.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Developer – Coding (Boot Camp Course)

December 2022 – June 2023

University of Toronto, ON

Chemical Laboratory Technology - Pharmaceutical (3 years)

September 2016 - April 2019

Seneca College, Toronto ON

Graduated with an overall 3.4 GPA.

CORE COMPETENCIES

- Strong written and verbal communications, active listening skills.
- Proficient Analytical skills and Analytical thinking abilities.
- Computer Proficiency (including Microsoft Office)
- Excellent interpersonal and organizational skills.
- Practical knowledge of HACCP, GMP & SOP's.
- Exceptional time management and holds the goal-oriented attitude.
- Perform daily audit for GMP, Non-compliances and food safety based on FGF standards.
- Fast learner with an energetic work attitude, flexibility, team player with strong work ethics.
- Play integral part of internal audit conducted by HACCP team.

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: JavaScript, CSS, HTML, Progressive web application (PWAs)
- Frameworks/Libraries: React/jQuery, Bootstrap, Tailwind
- Tools: Visual Studio Code, Git, Heroku, GitHub pages, Shell Scripting, Continuous Integration, Debugging
- Database: MySQL, MongoDB
- Server-Side Development: Node.js, Express, Template EnginesMern Stack (MongoDB, Express.js, React.js,
- API Design: Client-Server ModelAPI, REST, JSON, AJAX, HTTP request methods, GraphQL, Insomnia, Postman

GitHub Link: https://github.com/Parth0415

Portfolio Link: https://parth0415.github.io/parthnewportfolio/

EXPERIENCE

QA Tech – Secretariat (Ace bakery)

(September 2022 - Present)

- Perform weekly environmental swabbing for all four Zones, ATP, and allergen swabbing.
- Report any cleanliness and GMP issues in scorecard.
- Address, inform and red flag any food safety and quality issue.
- Create OPL and train as required.
- Assist QA lead in investigating customer complaints.
- Perform daily task of COA Verification.
- Assist QA lead in commissioning activities of new equipment and a new manufacturing line.
- Work with Cross Functional teams including Sanitation, Maintenance, Operations, Building Support, OpEx and R&D.
- Knowledge regarding SAP.
- Ensure that safe working environment is maintained all the time.
- Lead training sessions for Cross Functional teams.
- Prepared Glass and Plastic Audit for new manufacturing lines.
- Prepare shift reports to keep QA team including leaders in loop regarding the food safety findings and non-compliances noticed during the shift.
- Trained TMs on Inspection findings of Audits of both Internal and Third party.
- Update documents and posters as required on floor.
- Daily, weekly & monthly QA tasks based on assigned Task List.
- Assisted and provided support during Internal Audit.
- Perform HACCP and GMP training for Team members or as assigned by QA Lead.
- Properly document all QA activities and tasks in timely manner.

QA Tech Co-op – Weston Foods and Ace bakery

(June 2022 – September 2022)

- Worked at Applewood, Hafiz, Secretariat & Weston foods (675 Fenmar).
- Performs process checks throughout production, packaging, sanitation, and warehouse.
- Checks includes GMP, verification of label and coding, Metal detection, food safety and quality issues, weight of the product.
- Performing thermometer, Luminometer, pH and scale calibration based on required frequency.
- Implement Hold procedures in Hold spreadsheet and SAP for suspect and affected products.
- Assisted and provided support during Internal Audit.
- Conduct Glass and Hard plastic audits based on required frequency.

Restaurant Manager – Tim Hortons

(April 2017 - Jan 2022)

- Work with other team members / assistant managers/ supervisors efficiently.
- Video tutorial on food safety, cleanliness, and workplace hazards.
- Part of Joint Health and safety committee (JHSC)
- Ensure food safety and quality is never compromised.
- Always lead audit from Public Health (yearly) and Steritech (quarterly Tim Horton's) for the store
- Recruit and train staff in job duties, food safety, health, and safety procedures.
- Maintained a clean and safe environment with professionalism in a fast-paced environment.
- Make sure sanitation procedure in place and observed food preparation and cooking procedures to ensure food safety and health.
- Leads by example and demonstrates the importance of treating every team member and guest with respect. Provides ongoing, specific direction to team members.